<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Bruce 2233</title>
    <link>https://bruce2233.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Bruce 2233</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bruce2233.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>https://bruce2233.github.io/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bruce2233.github.io/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://bruce2233.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bruce2233.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bruce2233.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bruce2233.github.io/</guid>
      <description>Contributing Changes and improvements are more than welcome! Feel free to fork and open a pull request.
Please follow the house rules to have a bigger chance of your contribution being merged.
House rules How to make changes  To make changes, create a new branch based on master (do not create one from gh-pages unless strictly necessary) and make them there, then create a Pull Request to master.
gh-pages is different from master in that it contains sharing features, analytics and other things that have no direct bearing with the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bruce2233.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bruce2233.github.io/</guid>
      <description>2048 &amp;ndash;岛石版 一键安装部署:
1  docker run --name 2048-nginx -d -p 8080:80 bruce996/2048   A small clone of 1024, based on Saming&amp;rsquo;s 2048 (also a clone).
Made just for fun. Play it here!
The official app can also be found on the Play Store and App Store!
Contributions Anna Harren and sigod are maintainers for this repository.
Other notable contributors:
 TimPetricola added best score storage chrisprice added custom code for swipe handling on mobile marcingajda made swipes work on Windows Phone mgarciaisaia added support for Android 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://bruce2233.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bruce2233.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>To use this feature, add links section to frontmatter.
This page&amp;rsquo;s frontmatter:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9  links:- title:GitHubdescription:GitHub is the world&amp;#39;s largest software development platform.website:https://github.comimage:https://github.githubassets.com/images/modules/logos_page/GitHub-Mark.png- title:TypeScriptdescription:TypeScript is a typed superset of JavaScript that compiles to plain JavaScript.website:https://www.typescriptlang.orgimage:ts-logo-128.jpg  image field accepts both local and external images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://bruce2233.github.io/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bruce2233.github.io/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
